&gt；&gt；steve kinney：它运行得很好，对吧，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: It runs okay, right,
不是很好，这不是JavaScript真正快速的原因。
not great that's not what
makes JavaScript really fast.
使JavaScript真正快速的是那个绿色的箭头。
What makes JavaScript really
fast is that green arrow.
我们能越过那个绿色箭头到涡轮风扇的任何东西都是好的，对吧？
Anything we can get across that green
arrow to turbo fan is good, right?
[笑]只要我们能做到这一点，那就是我们想要做的事情。
[LAUGH] Whenever we can do that,
that is a thing that we want to do.
这是件好事。
That is a good thing.
因此，它提出了一个问题，我们如何做到这一点？
So then it raises the question,
how do we do that?
有很多，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：涡轮风扇和
There is a lot of the,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Turbo Fan and
V8作为一个整体主要是在德国制造的，[笑]尤其是慕尼黑。
V8 as a whole is mostly made in Germany,
[LAUGH] particularly Munich.
大部分的团队合作都在那里，这是一群非常好的人
Most of the teamwork's there, and
it's a bunch of really nice and
聪明人，我在那里工作的朋友，他们有博士和
smart people, friends of mine that
work there, and they have PhDs and
他们正在做一些非常技术性的事情。
they're doing some very technical stuff.
我们会像一个高级版本那样做，因为我
We're gonna do it like a high-level
version of that because I
渴望教你很多网络表现。
aspire to teach you a lot
of web performance.
如果我们都能带着博士离开这里，我绝对会这么做，但是
If we could all leave here with
PhDs I would totally do that, but
这可能不会发生。
that's probably not gonna happen.
所以我们将看看涡扇做的一些事情以及它是如何工作的。
So we're gonna look at a few of the things
that TurboFan does and how it works.
我们要看的三件事都是推测的。
The three things that we're
gonna look at are speculative.
我迫不及待地想说很多次
I can't wait to say that
a bunch of times in front of
一间满是人的房间被录音。
a room full of people being recorded.
推测性优化，隐藏类
Speculative optimization,
hidden classes for
动态查找和函数内联。
dynamic lookups and function inlining.
因为使优化编译器更快的原因是
Because the reason that what makes
the optimizing compiler faster is
类似的删除使解释器速度变慢的东西。
the like removal of the things
that make the interpreter slower.
因为JavaScript很难，JavaScript是动态的，JavaScript有很多规则。
Cuz JavaScript is hard and JavaScript is
dynamic and JavaScript has a lot of rules.
假设我们得到一个加法函数，对，加法x和y，它返回x+y。
So let's say we get an add function,
right, add x and y it returns x plus y.
你说是啊，这有什么难的？
You're like yeah, why is that hard?
加号运算符是做什么的？
Well, what does a plus operator do?
你就像是它增加了数字，我想，是的，如果我给它一些字符串呢？
You're like it adds numbers, I'm like,
yeah, what if I give it strings?
它将它们连接起来，好吧，如果我给它一个字符串和一个对象呢？
It concatenates them, okay,
what if I give it a string and an object?
嗯，它调用对象上的两个字符串，并且
Well, it calls two string on the object,
and
然后将其与第一个连接。
then concatenates that with the first one.
如果我给它一个数字和一串数字呢？
What if I give it a number and
a string of numbers?
JavaScript规范中有很多规则，对吧
There's a lot of rules, right,
in the JavaScript spec, and
翻译不知道，[笑]这里会发生什么，对吗？
the interpreter has no idea,
[LAUGH] what's gonna happen here, right?
它知道它必须添加x和y，它不一定知道x和y是什么，
It knows it has to add x and y, it doesn't
necessarily know what x and y are yet,
直到程序实际运行，所以它基本上必须遵循规则手册。
until the program's actually running, so
it basically has to follow the rule book.
但希望是，如果我们编写相同的函数1000，
But the hope is that,
if we are writing the same function, 1000,
10000，一百万次，我们可以开始做一些
10000, a million times,
that we can start to do like make some
猜测这里发生了什么，也许会跳过一些规则，对吧？
guesses on what's happening here,
and maybe skip some rules, right?
因为，有什么比做事情更快呢？
Because, what is faster than doing stuff?
不做事情，对吧，如果我们可以跳过所有那些疯狂的规则
Not doing stuff, right, and if we can
skip all of those kinda crazy rules and
串联和我是否需要抛出一个错误并为此做好准备。
concatenation and do I need to throw
an error and be ready for that.
如果我们能消除所有这些
If we can eliminate all of that,
我们可以更快地执行JavaScript，好吧，非常酷。
we can execute the JavaScript way faster,
all right, very cool.
因此，我们将继续查看一些代码。
So, we're gonna go ahead and
look at some code.
在，只是我们早些时候送出的
In the,
just that we've send out earlier for
观看这个然后它应该像下面的视频链接。
watching this then it should be
like a link below the video.
有一个叫做web-performance的回购，里面有一堆代码。
There is a repo called web-performance
with a bunch of code in it.
我们要玩弄这玩意儿
We're gonna play around with that for
等一下。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：在这里，
a second.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Here,
我有一个小文件，这是在该回购的基准目录中。
I have a little file this is in
the benchmarks directory in that repo.
这是一个名为Benchmark.js的文件，
This is a file called benchmark.js,
如你所知，我很擅长命名事物。
I'm very good with naming
things as you can tell.
我们实际上要看一些代码，那么这段代码中发生了什么？
And we're gonna actually look at some
code, so what's going on in this code?
第一件事是我们要把这个表演对象拉进来，
The first thing is we're gonna
pull in this performance object,
这不是一个MPM模块或沿这些路线的任何东西。
this is not an MPM module or
anything along those lines.
如果对于LTS的节点8.5和更高版本，
If you have for
the LTS's node 8.5 and later,
你有这个，我运行9.8，我有这个，对吧。
you have this, I'm running 9.8,
I have this, right.
因此，如果您有较早的版本，8.5和更高版本应该具有此功能，
So 8.5 and later should have this
if you have an earlier version,
你可能没有这个。
you might not have this.
你可能需要在休息时更新，我们一起做
And you might need to update during
the break and we'll do it together and
会很有趣的。
it'll be a lot of fun.
但是这个性能对象给了我们一大堆，它基本上实现了
But this performance object gives us
a whole bunch, it's basically implementing
所谓的用户计时API，在Chrome中也受支持。
what's called the user timing API,
which is also supported in Chrome.
所以，是的，如果您有现代版本的，这是特定于Node的版本
So yeah this is version is specific to
Node if you have a modern version of
Chrome你也有这些
Chrome you also have these
available as well and
你可以在你的控制台中运行其中的一些。
you can run some of these
maybe in your console.
酷，所以我们要把它放进去，然后我的基准测试中有一个小小的设置阶段
Cool, so we gonna pull that in, then I
have a little setup phase in my benchmark
在这里我要做一些科学记数法。
here where I'm gonna do one
some scientific notation a lot.
我是文科专业的，就像你刚从我可以翻译的事实中发现的那样
I'm a liberal arts major as you just found
out from the fact that I can translate
飞行中的科学记数法。
scientific notation on the fly.
我们做了很多次，我们只需要加1和2。
We did this a bunch of times and
we're just gonna add 1 and 2.
我们会循环一遍，把它们加在一起，
And we'll kinda go through in a loop,
add them together,
我们将结束性能基准测试，然后我们将度量它，并且
we'll end the performance benchmark,
and then we'll measure it, and
然后我们将控制台记录下测量结果，听起来不错吧？
then we'll console log that measurement,
sound good?
酷毙了。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：所以
Cool.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
我将继续，我将运行节点，我将只运行基准测试。
I'll go ahead and I'll run node,
and I'll just run the benchmarks.
酷，所以我在33毫秒内完成了所有这些。
Cool, so I did all of that
in about 33 milliseconds.
我将为用户计时API做一些快速的PSA
I'm gonna do a little kinda quick PSA for
the user timing API and
为什么它真的很酷。
why it's really cool.
我将采用这个代码，除了所需的普通js之外，
Which I'm gonna take this code,
other than the common js required,
因为我们知道这在浏览器中不受支持。
cuz we know that's not
supported in the browser.
我要拿走剩下的。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
I'm gonna take the rest of it.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
我要进入Chrome。
I'm gonna go ahead into Chrome.
转到大约空白。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我会
Go to about blank.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I'll
打开这里的工具，我可以贴进去，
open up the tools here,
and I could paste it in,
它运行，同样的时间，很好。
it runs, same amount of time, great.
但我想告诉你的是，我要去性能标签，
But what I wanna show you is,
I'm gonna go to the Performance tab,
我要开始录音了
I'm gonna start a recording.
这将是我们今天的朋友，我们会花很多时间
This is gonna be our friend today,
we're gonna spend a lot of time in
性能标签这是我们第一次尝试它。
the Performance tab this
is our first taste of it.
我要录音，然后我要去控制台。
I'm gonna record,
then I'm gonna go to Console.
不，我实际上你知道选择这里的控制台，我要录音，
No I actually you know pick
the console here, I'm gonna record,
我要把这个贴进去。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我要
I'm gonna paste this in.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I'm gonna
刷新页面，因为我使用了Constance，它不喜欢这样，再试一次。
refresh the page because I used constance
and it doesn't like that, one more try.
所以我们会录制，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们会把它粘贴进去
So we'll record,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We'll paste it in
点击Run我们会停下来。
hit Run we'll stop.
很酷，所以你可以看到我在这里做的这个JavaScript的尖峰。
Cool, so you can see I have this spike
of JavaScript that I'm doing here.
你可以看到它正在评估一个脚本，因为我刚刚把它粘贴到了
You can see it's evaluating a script
that's cuz I just pasted it into
控制台，所以它并不真正知道它是从哪里来的。
the console, so
it doesn't really know where it came from.
但我想提请你注意的是这里，对吧？
But what I want to draw your
attention to is right here, right?
我可以将自己的条目放入所谓的
I can put my own entries
into what's called
联合开发工具的用户计时部分，对吗？
the user timing portion of
the co-developer tools, right?
所以记得当我把这个敲回家的时候，嘿，让我们测量一下东西，
So remember when I was hammering home
this, hey, let's measure things,
你说，太好了，是的，我不知道怎么做整洁。
you're like, great, yeah,
I don't know how to do that neat.
如果计时真的有用，就使用计时
Use the timing if it has really useful for
这是因为你基本上可以设置你的标记开始时间，你标记结束时间，
this cuz you can basically set your
mark a start time, you mark an end time,
然后你可以做这个措施，你可以给它起任何你想要的名字。
and then you can do this measure where
you can give it whatever name you want.
我把它称为我的特别基准，让你相信我把这个放进去了
I called it my special benchmark to
have you believed me that I put this in
在那里，这不是Chrome的东西。
there and this was not a Chrome thing.
但实际上您可以将所有这些基准放入，以查看给定的
But you can actually put in all of these
benchmarks to see exactly how long a given
您的应用程序的操作正在进行。
action of your application is taking.
所以我想知道，嘿，我想这里有一些伤害，你可以放一个，
So I wanna know like, hey, I think some
of the hurt is here, you can put a,
你可以标记你认为正在受伤的事情的开始时间。
you can mark the start time of
the thing that you think is hurting.
你可以标记结束时间，实际上你可以把它放入Chrome
You can mark the end time and
you can actually put that into the Chrome
开发人员工具，做一个性能记录，然后看看这些事情
developer tools, do a performance
recording and then see when those things
正在发生，他们需要多长时间，对，这是非常有趣的。
are happening and how long they are
taking, right, which is super interesting.
也是一种非常好的调试方式，
And a really great way to debug,
我们稍后会看到，开发模式中的REACTION实际上使用了这个开箱即用的功能。
we'll see later that react actually in
development mode uses this out of the box.
因此，您可以实际看到组件何时开始安装，何时最终安装，
So you can actually see when a component
started mounting, when it finally mounted,
所有这些东西，它实际上也会在这里记录这些东西。
all those thing, it will actually
log those all here as well.
这对
Which is super useful for
弄清楚是不是你的反应代码里有什么东西在做这件事。
figuring out if it's something in
your reacticode that's doing this.
但是，是的，这真的是一个很好的工具，可以找出为什么某些东西
But yeah this is a really great tool for
figuring out why something that's taking
只要它是，如果它是需要很长时间的事情，等等。
as long as it is, if it's the thing taking
a long time, and so on and so forth.
但是回到我们的主要活动，所以在这里，我们运行它，
But back to our main event,
so here, we ran it,
如果我们知道这里发生了什么，比如这个代码，那就太好了？
it'd be really great if we knew like what
was happening here, like is this code?
我的意思是，有人会争论这个代码，
I mean, one would argue this code,
我们只是用相同的变量运行相同的函数，很多次，
that we're just running the same function
with the same variables, a lot of times,
感觉它是去优化编译器的一个很好的候选者，对吧。
it feels like it's a good candidate for
going to the optimizing compiler, right.
我们如何知道它是否会进入优化编译器，我们知道吗？
How do we know if it's going to
the optimizing compiler, do we know?
是不是就像史蒂夫告诉我们的那样
Is it just like,
Steve told us that things go there and
他看起来很有信心，因此它必须，对吧。
he seems confident,
thereby it must, right.
或者，我们如何判断是否有东西进入了优化编译器？
Or how can we tell if something's
going to the optimizing compiler?
事实证明，V8有一堆标志，您可以
It turns out that V8 has
a bunch of flags that you can
设置以获取关于正在发生的事情的更多信息。
set to get more information
about what's going on.
例如，我们可以做节点并获得这个标志跟踪opy，
So for instance we could do node and
get this flag trace opy,
有人猜到traced opt代表什么了吗？&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：trace
anyone guessed what traced opt stands for?
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Trace
优化。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：会更容易
optimizations.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: There will be an easier
稍后的问题，你们都可以用来救赎自己。
question later that you can all
like redeem yourselves with.
很酷，你可以看到这里有一些东西被记录到控制台上。
Cool, and you can see there's some
stuff being logged to the console here.
我对第一个很感兴趣
I'm kind of interested
in this first one which
是否标记JavaScript函数add。
is the JavaScript function
add is being marked.
我们将add函数标记为优化重新编译，原因是什么？
We're marking the add function for
optimized recompilation, reasons?
这是一个小函数，有内联缓存，
It's a small function,
there's in-line caching,
我们一会儿再谈。
which we'll talk about in a second.
所以，是的，我们做了，我们用Turbo Fan编译它，
So yeah, we do it,
we compile it with Turbo Fan,
它完成了优化很酷。
it completes the optimizing very cool.
还有一些其他的事情。
There's some other things.
有一个调试工具叫D8，用于调试V8，CATE。
There is a debugging tool called D8
which is used for debugging V8, cute.
它更加专业，但你必须下载它，编译Chrome和
That it was much more specialized but you
have to download it, compile Chrome and
一堆东西。
a bunch of stuff.
如果你真的喜欢这个，这绝对是你想要的方向，
If you get really into this that's
definitely the way you wanna go,
因为Node不仅仅是V8，它也是Node。
because Node is not just V8,
but it's also Node.
所以这里的其他东西实际上是Node发生的。
So this other stuff here
is actually Node happening.
因此，如果我们是命令行向导，可以做的一件有用的事情就是运行它。
So a useful thing to do, if we're
command-line wizards, is to run it.
我们可以执行grep add，它将查找具有函数名称的每一行
And we can do grep add, which will find
every line with the name of the function
在里面，我们会得到更少的噪音。
in it, and
we'll get a little bit less noise.
所以在这里你可以看到之前信息的子集，好吗？
So here you can see the Subset of
the previous information, okay?
我们为重新编译优化了add，我们现在知道它去了turbofan，
We optimized add for recompilation,
we now know that it went to TurboFan,
它得到了优化。
it got optimized.
它去了优化编译器很好，摇滚乐。
It went to to the optimizing
compiler good, rock and roll.